<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Medireview Test]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Medireview Test]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/medireview/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 19:22:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/medireview/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pain Killers are out of Control]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Pain Killers are out of Control</h1><p>On October 3 2014 Carly Weeks of The Globe and Mail brought to light the dangerous and life threatening trend of Canadian doctors over prescribing high-dose opioids. It sounds like some of these doctors are carelessly sticking to this dangerous norm despite the real risks faced by the patients who rely on them for professional advice.</p><img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/3458370296_1085f1bc8f_o.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://medireview.com/2014/10/pain-killers-are-out-of-control/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">497d1c27-2204-4918-9afa-34969444c019</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 19:20:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shedding the Stigma at Toronto Sick Kids' Hospital?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Shedding the Stigma at Toronto Sick Kids' Hospital?</h1><p>The subject of marijuana is tricky enough as it is without introducing children into the mix, but it's necessary because there are significant benefits to be had. Granted it's anecdotal, but it is becoming more and more documented, and now even the American Association of Pediatrics is recommending to the Drug Enforcement Agency that cannabis should be removed from the highly restrictive Schedule I classification so more research can be performed.</p><img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/3994070297_6c7419b52d_o.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://medireview.com/2015/02/shedding-the-stigma-at-toronto-sick-kids-hospital/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ecde1cdb-c21a-4de5-a07b-22365b81e2d4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 19:20:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical Marijuana for Addiction is Gaining Traction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Medical Marijuana for Addiction is Gaining Traction</h1><p>The jury is still out about weather Medical Marijuana can be addictive, however when you compare the addictiveness of marijuana with alcohol, there doesn't seem to be much of a comparison. A staggering 50% of alcoholics will relapse with in 6 months.</p><img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/3121533608_77a8aea493_b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://medireview.com/2015/02/medical-marijuana-for-addiction-is-gaining-traction/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6b158e00-2842-4653-9674-319b93f6723d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 19:20:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[92% of patients say medical marijuana works]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>92% of patients say medical marijuana works</h1><p>Today the Washington Post reported that 92% of patients surveyed in California say that medical marijuana alleviated symptoms of their serious medical conditions, including chronic pain, arthritis, migraine, and cancer.</p><img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/9181427404_4fce7189b0_o.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://medireview.com/2014/10/92-of-patients-say-medical-marijuana-works/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">859f5b45-61ab-4ebc-a41a-190ddcc70b0d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 19:19:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>DOES MEDICAL MARIJUANA HELP? IT’S COMPLICATED   by CHRIS DOLLARD JULY 22, 2015 Share on twitterShare on printShare on facebookShare on flipboardMore Sharing Services 0 (Photo: Kelly Wilkinson/The Star) I struggle with the issue of legalization of marijuana, knowing what I know as a physician, but understanding the problems associated with its continued status as an illegal drug. For now, permit me to discuss medical marijuana, its potential medical uses, and suggest one change in federal regulation. The tide has turned in America regarding attitudes toward marijuana. Medical marijuana is now legal in 23 states, and in the near future, medical marijuana will be legal in the majority of states. Colorado, Alaska, Washington, Oregon, and the District of Columbia have legalized recreational use; more than 14 states are now considering legalization of medical or recreational marijuana. A national survey of physicians’ attitudes and beliefs regarding medical marijuana was recently released. Nearly 70 percent of physicians questioned believed that marijuana possesses therapeutic benefits and 49 percent indicated that the benefits outweigh the risks (many physicians did indicate concerns about untoward effects). Sixty-eight percent of physicians in the study responded that marijuana should be a medical option, and when asked if it should be legalized, just over half of physicians answered affirmatively. Surprisingly, a higher percentage of physicians believed that marijuana possesses therapeutic benefits than did lay people questioned in the study. That being said, review of the medical literature indicates that the legalization of medical and recreational marijuana remains very controversial. From discussions with Indiana physicians, it appears that they have a more negative opinion of marijuana compared to the national survey. Marijuana and synthetic pharmaceutical cannabinoids (two approved by the FDA and others available in other countries) have demonstrated evidence-based medical benefits for specific ailments by legitimate scientific studies. There are also ample additional credible empirical reports for smoked marijuana. It should be noted that some of the studies used oral pharmaceutical cannabinoid products, […]  Click here to view original web page at www.indystar.com</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/medireview/does-medical-marijuana-help-its-complicated-by-chris-dol/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02a72830-f4f2-41b7-ab01-2d459bc8abf6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 18:48:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domestic Violence Reduced with Medical Marijuana?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Domestic Violence Reduced with Medical Marijuana?</h1><p>Philip H. Smith, Ph.D, an associate research scientist in the Department of Psychiatry at Yale University, working in the Yale Global Mental Health Program has published a study showing that young married couples in the first 9 years of marriage who both smoke marijuana have lower incidents of domestic violence.</p><img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/4729125052_24ac515700_o.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://medireview.com/2015/02/domestic-violence-reduced-with-medical-marijuana/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7b44004b-2c8b-44f8-8896-34026f7b71a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 18:44:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://medireview.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/TMMR_logowebrd.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/medireview/0af98c9e-f753-4dfb-a251-244fc75d6da9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0af98c9e-f753-4dfb-a251-244fc75d6da9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 18:43:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Test 1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Test 1</h1><p>This is a new post to test the grid.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/medireview/test-1/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">16ec9974-7eae-4a99-b416-7960d4229da4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 18:39:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>